AoM Additional copy of publications on Microfilm 5977 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
AoM Additional copy of publications on Microfilm
1948-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Academy of Management (AoM)
5977 mf
8.11 cubic feet
73 microfilm reels
Records.
Collection consists of mircofilm copies of various Academy of Management periodicals.
5743748
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 10, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 10, 2016
Biographical / Historical
Since its beginning in 1936, the Academy has evolved from an organization of 10 members to an organization of over 19,000 members from nearly 120 nations. Today, the Academy's 25 professional divisions and interest groups promote excellence in established management disciplines. Five U.S.-based affiliates, the Eastern, Midwest, Southwest, and Western Academies of Management and the Southern Management Association as well as two international affiliates, the Asia and Iberoamerican Academies of Management, promote the exchange of ideas and provide collaborative opportunities for colleagues sharing a geographic area, language, or cultural identity. The Academy of Management continues to support scholarly activity and the exchange of ideas through our divisions and interest groups; annual meeting; Academy of Management News; listservs; AOM Online; collaborative activities with affiliated and associated societies; and five journals: the Academy of Management Annals, Academy of Management Learning and Education (AMLE), Academy of Management Journal (AMJ), Academy of Management Review (AMR); Academy of Management Perspectives (AMP) - formerly the Academy of Management Executive (AME).
The Academy of Management is located on the Briarcliff Manor, New York, Campus of Pace University.
Scope and Contents
This is a collection of microfilm copies of Academy of Management Publications: Proceedings (1948-1985) + Index; Best Papers Proceedings (1986-1994); Journal (v.1-18, 22-23 - 1958-1980) + Index; Executive (v.1-9); Review (v.6-15)
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Professional associations -- United States -- Administration.; Academy of Management.
5743748
- Academy of Management Proceedings -- 1948-1971 (Reel 1)
- Academy of Management Proceedings -- 1976 (Reel 2)
- Academy of Management Proceedings -- 1977 (Reel 3)
- Academy of Management Proceedings -- 1978 (Reel 4)
- Academy of Management Proceedings -- 1979 (Reel 5)
- Academy of Management Proceedings -- 1980 + Index (Reel 6)
- Academy of Management Proceedings -- 1981 (Reel 7)
- Academy of Management Proceedings -- 1982 (Reel 8)
- Academy of Management Proceedings -- 1983 (Reel 9)
- Academy of Management Proceedings -- 1984 (Reel 10)
- Academy of Management Proceedings -- 1985 (Reel 11)
- Academy of Management Best Papers Proceedings -- 1986 (Reel 12)
- Academy of Management Best Papers Proceedings -- 1987 (Reel 13)
- Academy of Management Best Papers Proceedings -- 1988 (Reel 14)
- Academy of Management Best Papers Proceedings -- 1989 (Reel 15)
- Academy of Management Best Papers Proceedings -- 1990 (Reel 16)
- Academy of Management Best Papers Proceedings -- 1991 (Reel 17)
- Academy of Management Best Papers Proceedings -- 1992 (Reel 18)
- Academy of Management Best Papers Proceedings -- 1994 (Reel 19)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.1-11 (Apr. 1958-Dec. 1968) + Index (Reel 20)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.12-17 (Mar.1969-Dec.1974) + Index (Reel 21)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.18-22 (1975-Dec. 1979) + Index (Reel 22)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.24 (Mar.-Dec. 1981) + Index (Reel 23)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.25 (Mar.-Dec. 1982) + Index (Reel 24)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.26 (Mar.-Dec. 1983) + Index (Reel 25)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.27 (Mar.-Dec. 1984) + Index (Reel 26)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.28 (Mar.-Dec. 1985) + Index (Reel 27)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.29 (Mar.-Dec. 1986) + Index (Reel 28)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.30 (Mar.-Dec. 1987) + Index (Reel 29)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.31 (Mar.-Dec. 1988) + Index (Reel 30)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.32 (Mar.-Dec. 1989) + Index (Reel 31)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.33 (Mar.-Dec. 1990) + Index (Reel 32)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.34 (Mar.-Dec. 1991) + Index (Reel 33)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.35 (Mar.-Dec. 1992) + Index (Reel 34)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.36 (Feb.-Dec. 1993) + Index (Reel 35)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.37 (Feb.-Dec. 1994) + Index (Reel 36)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.38 (Feb.-Dec. 1995) + Index (Reel 37)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.15, 1-4 March-Dec. 1972 Index (Reel 38)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.16, 1-4 March-Dec. 1973 Index (Reel 39)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.16, 1-4 March-Dec. 1973 Index (Reel 40)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.17, 1-4 March-Dec. 1974 Index (Reel 41)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.18, 1-4 March-Dec. 1975 Index (Reel 42)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.22, 1-4 Index March-Dec. 1979 (Reel 43)
- Academy of Management Journal -- v.23, 1-4 Index March-Dec. 1980 (Reel 44)
- Academy of Management Executive -- v.1 (Feb-Nov 1987) (Reel 45)
- Academy of Management Executive -- v.2 (Feb-Nov 1988) + Index (Reel 46)
- Academy of Management Executive -- v.3 (Feb-Nov 1989 + Index (Reel 47)
- Academy of Management Executive -- v.4 (Feb-Nov 1990) + Index (Reel 48)
- Academy of Management Executive -- v.5 (Feb-Nov 1991) + Index (Reel 49)
- Academy of Management Executive -- v.6 (Feb-Nov 1992) + Index (Reel 50)
- Academy of Management Executive -- v.7 iss. 1 (Feb 1993) + Index (Reel 51)
- Academy of Management Executive -- v.7 iss 2-4 (May-Nov 1993) + Index (Reel 52)
- Academy of Management Executive -- v.8 (Feb-Nov 1994) (Reel 53)
- Academy of Management Executive -- v.9 (Feb-Nov 1995) (Reel 54)
- Academy of Management Review -- v.6 (Jan-Oct 1981) + Index (Reel 55)
- Academy of Management Review -- v.7 (Jan-Oct 1981) + Index (Reel 56)
- Academy of Management Review -- v.8 (Jan-Oct 1983) + Index (Reel 57)
- Academy of Management Review -- v.9 (Jan-Oct 1984) + Index (Reel 58)
- Academy of Management Review -- v.10 (Jan-Oct 1985) + Index (Reel 59)
- Academy of Management Review -- v.11 (Jan-Oct 1986) + Index (Reel 60)
- Academy of Management Review -- v.12 (Jan-Oct 1987) + Index (Reel 61)
- Academy of Management Review -- v.13 (Jan-Oct 1988) + Index (Reel 62)
- Academy of Management Review -- v.14 (Jan-Oct 1989) + Index (Reel 63)
- Academy of Management Review -- v.15 (Jan-Oct 1990) + Index (Reel 64)
- Academy of Management Review -- v.16 (Jan-Oct 1991) + Index (Reel 65)
- Academy of Management Review -- v.17 (Jan-Oct 1992) + Index (Reel 66)
- Academy of Management Review -- v.18 (Jan-Oct 1993) + Index (Reel 67)
- Academy of Management Review -- v.19 (Jan-Oct 1994) + Index (Reel 68)
- Academy of Management Review -- v.1, 1-4 Jan-Oct 1976 Index (Reel 69)
- Academy of Management Review -- v.2, 1-4 Jan-Oct 1977 Index (Reel 70)
- Academy of Management Review -- v.3, 1-4 Jan-Oct 1978 Index (Reel 71)
- Academy of Management Review -- v.4, 1-4 Index Jan-Oct 1979 (Reel 72)
- Academy of Management Review -- v.5, 1-4 Index Jan-Oct 1980 (Reel 73)